hi everyone I want to tell you about an
event that's going to take place in
Toronto on July 18th at 7:30 p.m. it's
going to be held at the Canada Christian
College 50 Gervais Drive in Toronto the
event is entitled bill C 16 one year
later
sex ideology and compelled speech in
Canada and here's the background detail
bill C 16 has incorporated gender
identity and expression into Canadian
human rights law in the criminal code
within a broader policy context
predicated on the idea that gender is
solely a social construct the effect is
rippling through the social world
affecting schools universities the
healthcare systems the law and
journalism what implications does this
have for free speech what punitive
measures can and does the law impose on
those who violate its provisions there
is no scientific evidence that supports
the idea that gender and sex and biology
and sexual proclivity vary independently
but that position is now instantiated
into Canadian law the following four
panelists will discuss these issues and
more Lyndsey Shepherd Lyndsey rose to
prominence after staff at Wilfrid
Laurier University subjected her to a
disciplinary hearing for showing a video
discussing Bill c16 to her students
while she was serving as a teaching
assistant that produced the biggest
scandal in Canadian university history
and very little evidence by the way that
Wilfrid Laurier University learned it's
lesson she will be speaking at this
event about the tactics and effects of
trans activism on university campuses
Barbara Kaye will also speak she's a
teacher author and an influential
columnist for the Canadian newspaper the
National Post she will be speaking on
the impact suppression of free speech is
having on journalism illustrating with
the personal experiences she and others
have had in the areas of indigenous
correctness she was fired as a regular
contributor to a CBC radio show for
incorrect remarks made elsewhere she
will speak about the phenomenon known in
Arabic
as kept Minh defined by one scholar as
the position taken by those who desire
to be at one with others in order not to
be alone dr. Debra Sol will speak as
well she holds a PhD from York
University and writes about the science
and politics of sex and culture dr. Sol
is a columnist for Playboy comm and The
Globe and Mail her writing has been
widely featured in such publications as
Harper's The Wall Street Journal and the
LA Times she will be discussing the
science of gender what makes someone
feel female or male and why gender
ideology which denies the influence of
biology is harmful as she states the
common belief nowadays is that gender is
a spectrum and that sexual orientation
gender identity and gender expression
are unrelated this is not what the
scientific research indicates Jared
Brown rounds out the panel he's lead
counsel at Brown litigation aiding his
clients in matters relating to
commercial and employment disputes
breaches of contract shareholder
disputes and collection of accounts last
year he spoke to the Canadian Senate
about the dangers of bill c16 Jared will
be speaking about the legal aspects of
c16 including its legislation of
compelled speech the opinions of
Canadian and US courts regarding such
speech and his experience of the
subterfuge and dishonesty of the
proponents of the legislation in his
words the politicking behind the scenes
of my appearance at the Senate made it
clear that the intention of the
proponents was to control speech all
along
Serena Singh will moderate Serena
is an ex social worker and an emerging
political and social commentator she
organized the largest discussion on free
speech ever held in Canada on November
11th 2017 as well as this one year later
event I'm really interested in this
gathering I'm going to try to make it at
least to attend and listen although I'm
coming back from London that day and if
there's any delays I won't be able to
manage it but I would strongly encourage
everyone who can manage it to go and
listen to these panelists it's an
important discussion and it should be an
extraordinarily interesting event thanks
for your attention
bye-bye